thefullwiki.org 2019-06-17

# Privacy Policy

We will not pass on your email address or personal details to third parties, unless requested by law enforcement agencies or otherwise required by law. Further, we will not use them for advertising unrelated products. We may however, use your details and site activity to improve the service and we may report aggregates to others (eg. number of signups from a particular postcode). 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

You may unsubscribe from our mailing list and/or subscription service at any time. 

Exponential Interactive, Inc, as our partner, have a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. For more details including opt-out requests, access requests or complaints, please review their [privacy policy](http://exponential.com/privacy/) or contact their data protection officer via [privacy@exponential.com](mailto:privacy@exponential.com). 

Subject to your consent, Exponential Interactive, Inc collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. You may change your consent decision at any time via . For more details including access requests and complaints, review their [privacy policy](http://exponential.com/privacy/) or contact their data protection officer via [privacy@exponential.com](mailto:privacy@exponential.com).
